nimbusweb.me 2019-08-27

# Nimbus - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting NimbusWeb.me, Nimbusweb.com and/or EverHelper.me, nimbusmind.com, nimbusweb.co, fvdspeeddial.com, livestartpage,com (collectively, the “Websites”) and/or one of our interconnected programs, such as Nimbus Note, Nimbus Clipper, Nimbus Capture, and others (collectively, the “Products”), whether you access them online or by downloading the Product to your computer and/or mobile device. The Websites and Products are provided to you by Nimbus Web, Inc. (“Nimbus Web,” “we,” “us” and “our”). 

We provide this Privacy Policy to explain how Nimbus Web collects, uses and shares information from you when you use the Websites and Products and to help you make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Websites and Products. 

**1\. Who controls the information collected about me?**

Any personal information provided to or gathered by Nimbus Web is controlled by:   
Nimbus Web Inc  
50 Public Square, Suite 200, Cleveland OH 44113  
UNITED STATES   
legal@nimbusweb.co 

**2\. What information does Nimbus Web collect from me and why?**

The amount and type of information we gather depends upon your use of the Websites and Products and, in some cases, what type of information you choose to disclose. We may collect the following information from you:

**Personal Information Voluntarily Provided by You**

We collect information from you when you register with Nimbus Web to create an online account and/or when you submit your personal information to us over the Websites or through the Products. You will always be aware when you are providing such information because you will be required to type it in or otherwise submit it yourself. Such personal information may include your name, email and postal addresses, phone number, payment and billing information, Product purchased, and other information which you voluntarily provide to us. 

For example, when you first create an account with us, we will ask you to enter your email address and create a password to be associated with your account. If you order any Product from us, we will also ask you to provide the necessary payment details, such as your credit or debit card and billing address, so that your order can be processed. 

**Information You Choose to Make Public**

From time to time, whether now or in the future, the Website and Products may contain features that permit you to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, media, or other information, including any personal information you choose to disclose through such features. Any information that you choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which Nimbus Web is unable to exercise control, because at that point, any other user could copy and disseminate the information. You should take caution when deciding to disclose your personal information by means of such features For example, the Website may allow you to post a public-facing review of a particular Product. if you use your real name (or a variation thereon) as your username to post such a review, you are making your personal information public. 

**Information About Your Device, Internet Connection and Access of the Websites and Products**

When you use the Websites or Products, we automatically gather information made available by your web browser (such as Microsoft Edge or Google Chrome), Internet service provider (such as Comcast or Time Warner), and device (such as your computer, phone, or tablet), depending on your settings for each. For example, we may collect your IP address, information about the operating system or type of device you use, the date and time you access the Websites or Products, and the location of your device. 

Generally, the information addressed under this section is anonymous and does not, standing alone, directly identify you; however, it could possibly identify you when associated with other information. For example, if a third party were to see your IP address, they would not automatically know your name—yet your name could be associated with your IP address by your Internet service provider if you are the named accountholder.

**Information About You Provided to Us by Third Parties**

Nimbus Web may receive information about you and your Internet activities if you have provided it to a third party (each, a “Third Party”) and we subsequently acquire the information from the Third Party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your personal and online interests, and Internet browsing habits. These Third Parties may have collected such information from you directly (such as when you registered with their websites) or by placing Cookies on your device, using web beacons, gathering IP addresses and log data, and so forth. 

The purpose of this practice, which is sometimes called “retargeting,” is to deliver content and advertising that is specific to your interests. For example, if you look at a particular Product on the Website, you may later see that same Product advertised to you on Facebook. You can better learn about such Third-Party data collection and advertising practices, including how to opt-out of retargeting, at the following websites: 

http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices   
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices   
http://www.aboutads.info/choices 

**Payment Information**

All payments are processed by third-party vendors, including Recurly, Walletone and Stripe, and not Nimbus Web itself. If you make a purchase on the Websites or through the Products, credit card numbers and related information, such as billing address, card number, and the expiration date of the card (“Credit Card Information”) is collected from you, but such information is sent directly from you to our payment processors through embeddable widgets and is never stored or otherwise retained by Nimbus Web. 

**Job Applicant Information**

If you apply for a job with Nimbus Web, you will be asked to submit personal information, including identifying and employment information, as part of the application process (“Job Applicant Information”). Job Applicant Information will be used solely in connection with the consideration of your application for the position at issue. We may retain your Job Applicant Information, but only for the purpose of considering your application for future available positions. 

Although there may be some crossover in terms of the personal information collected from you as a user of the Website or Products and your Job Application Information (for example, your name and email address), Job Application is treated as separate and apart from all other information addressed in this Privacy Policy. 

**Other Information**

From time to time, we may obtain other information from you, such as when you make a claim for a prize pursuant to a contest or other promotion run on the Websites, when you request assistance through from our customer service department with one of the Products, and when you voluntarily subscribe to a Nimbus Web service or newsletter. You will always be asked to provide such other information voluntarily, and we will not collect it without your permission.

**3\. How does Nimbus Web use Cookies and Web Beacons to collect information about me?**

“Cookies” are files that are placed on your device by websites you visit. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify you as a unique user of the Websites or online instances of the Products. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to, among other things, transfer an individual’s unique user identification (often in the form of a Cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows us to track certain websites you visit online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services you may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes.

We currently use Cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information we already have in our database, for the following purposes:

To Facilitate Your Use of the Website. We use Cookies to make it so you do not have to reenter your login and/or other information repeatedly. For example, we may use a Session ID to remember your search terms for the duration of your session using the Website. If you have created a user account, Cookies make it so that you do not have to reenter your login information each time you use the Websites or Products.

To Analyze User Trends. We also use Cookies for analytics and performance—that is, to gather information that helps us understand how you and other users engage with the Websites and Products and figure out how to do it better. The Third Party analytics vendors we work with include Google Analytics, MixPanel, Flurry, AppSee, Appsflyer, Fabric, Facebook Analyticsm and others.

To Provide Support to You. We also use Cookies, including those placed by Third Party customer support vendors, to provide customer support services. 

To Advertise to You. We also use Cookies and web beacons, including those placed by Third Parties, to deliver advertising that may be of interest to you. For example, we use the Facebook web beacon to better target and retarget users and potential users of the Websites by advertising to them on Facebook. Twitter, Google Analytics, Google Adwords, and other Third Party Cookies may also be used in our advertising endeavors. We may also use a web beacon in email messages sent to track your response. Cookies and web beacons also help us and our Third-Party advertising partners ensure you do not see the same advertisements over and over and to identify and block unwanted ads. 

**4\. How does Nimbus Web use my information?**

We use the information we’ve gathered from you, including through Cookies and web beacons, for the following purposes:

**To Communicate with You**

We use information gathered on the Websites and through the Products to personalize communication with you, and to respond to your requests for products, services, and information. When you provide your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number to us through one of the Websites or Products, you may be asked if you consent to receive advertising emails or other electronic communications from us. If you consent, you can always unsubscribe to advertising emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link within the email, or by contacting us at team@nimbusweb.co Please note that, even if you unsubscribe from advertising emails, we will still send you any necessary, non-promotional emails about your account or updates to our privacy policy and terms.

**To Improve the Websites**

Nimbus Web uses the information we collect from you and other users to provide and improve the Websites and Products. As explained above, we use Cookies, including those placed by Third Parties, to gather statistical information that helps us understand how you and other users engage with the Websites and Products and improve their performance.

**To Personalize Your User Experience**

We use information gathered from Cookies to determine whether you are logged in or not, and to allow you to set personal preferences when using the Websites and Products, including how long you stay logged in.

**To Advertise to You**

As explained above, we use information gathered through Cookies and web beacons, including those placed by Third Parties, to deliver ads to you. Such advertising allows us to monetize the Website and Products and keep Product pricing low. 

**5\. How does Nimbus Web share my information with Third Parties?**

**To Fulfill Your Information Requests and Orders**

We may transfer your information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a Product or service that you order or request from us. For example, as explained above, your Credit Card Information is automatically transferred directly to our Third-Party payment processors through the Websites.

**To Advertise to Others**

We may share your reviews and comments about Nimbus Web to advertise and market our products and services. If you want us to stop using the personal data you have provided in these ways, please contact us at team@nimbusweb.co

**To Our Affiliated Companies**

We may disclose, transfer, and assign your information to our affiliated entities—that is, businesses that have common ownership with us—at our discretion, in which event, your information shall be treated by the affiliated entities in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Should Nimbus Web be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, we reserve the right to transfer or assign your information as part of that acquisition, merger or sale.

**To Our Third Party Partners**

We may disclose your personal information as needed to our Third-Party service providers and advertising partners. For example, if you have consented to receive promotional emails from us, we may share your email address with the Third-Party fulfillment provider that manages our email campaigns. 

**To Comply with Legal Process and Prevent Harm**

We may disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes. In rare circumstances, and only where lawful, we may disclose personal information when we believe it is necessary in order to prevent illegal, fraudulent, or injurious actions that may cause harm to individuals.

Nimbus will have no rights or licenses to use personally identifiable information other than for the delivery and functioning of the product

**6\. Where does Nimbus Web store my information?**

Nimbus Web stores your personal information in the United States. If you are visiting the Websites or using the Products from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using the Websites and Products, you authorize and specifically consent to the transfer of personal information to the United States and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us.

**7\. How does Nimbus Web protect my information?**

Nimbus Web, and the Third-Party vendors we use to store your information, employ security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. For example, user passwords are stored securely as BCrypt hashes. Credit Card Information is stored by our Third-Party payment processors, Stripe, WalletOne and Recurly, pursuant to PCI-DSS Level 1 standards. Access to the Websites and our API is made through HTTPS protocol and SSL encryption. We also use end-to-end encryption. Users encrypt their data with their password and encryption certificate, and Nimbus Web is unable to decrypt it without the corresponding password. 

Although Nimbus Web uses industry standard security practices, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personal and commercial information, or other communications, will always remain secure. 

In addition to these technical measures, Nimbus takes internal measures, including background checks and security training of those that have access to personal data. 

We are committed to complying with the student data privacy laws that apply to your use of Nimbus and helping our customers comply with FERPA. 

In the unlikely event that we go out of business, or file for bankruptcy, we will protect your personal information, and will not sell it to any third-party. 

In the event that Nimbus is sold or merged with another company, we will continue to protect your personal information, and will ensure that transfer of any data is done securely. 

**8\. How can I access or correct my information?**

You may access all information we’ve collected about you for purposes of correcting, transferring, amending, or deleting such information. Access can be obtained by contacting legal@nimbusweb.co. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information to the Websites may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at legal@nimbusweb.co. 

All data provided by you will continue to be under your control. 

**9\. How does Nimbus Web protect the privacy of children?**

Nimbus Web will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. We have designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

**10\. Does Nimbus Web respond to Do Not Track (DNT) Signals?**

DNT is a feature offered by some browsers which, when enabled, sends a signal to websites to request that your browsing is not tracked. Nimbus Web does not currently respond to DNT requests. 

**11\. What about Third Party practices?**

**Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons**

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, “Third Parties”) who place advertisements on the Websites and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Except as expressly provided herein, we do not control Third Parties’ use of such technology and we have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. It is up to you to familiarize yourself with the privacy practices of such Third Parties. 

**Third Party  Links **

The Websites and promotional email may contain hypertext links to the Websites of Third Parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third-Party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

**12\. How will I find out about changes to the Privacy Policy?**

Each time you use the Websites or Products, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Although most changes are likely to be minor, we reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy by posting such modification on the Websites; however, if changes are significant, we may provide a more prominent notice or email you. Unless we receive your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier version. 

**13\. Data Breach**

Within 48 hours of learning about a data breach, or longer reasonable time as may be required, we will notify all Users whose information may have been improperly disclosed, via email communication to the email address on file for each User. This email notification will describe the nature of the data breach, the date of the breach, the types of information that were subject to the breach, and steps that are being taken to protect your account going forward. 

In our commitment to protect the privacy of children, we participate in the iKeepSafe Safe Harbor program. If you have any questions or need to file a complaint related to our privacy policy and practices, please contact the iKeepSafe Safe Harbor program’s dedicated consumer complaint department at [COPPAPrivacy@ikeepsafe.org](mailto:COPPAPrivacy@ikeepsafe.org)

**Contact Us regarding any questions or concerns about this policy or your privacy**

Nimbus Web Inc  
50 Public Square, Suite 200, Cleveland OH 44113  
UNITED STATES  
(216) 438-1917  
team@nimbusweb.co
